

Piotr Skrzypa

Senior Unity Developer



+48 723 497 731



skrzypapiotr144@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/piotr-skrzypa



🔰 github.com/PiotrSkrzypa



piotrskrzypa.github.io

Summary

For 8 years, I have been creating games with Unity, including over 6 years professionally. I have worked on productions for mobile platforms, PC, VR, and consoles. I have participated in the full game development cycle — from designing architecture, through implementing mechanics and user interfaces, to debugging and optimization. I also have experience in managing development teams and creating developer tools.

Skills

- Unity
- Visual Studio
- C#
- GIT
- Addressables
- Shader Graph
- VFX Graph

- UniTask
- Zenject
- UniRx / R3
- Odin Inspector
- Porting to consoles
- Teamwork

Experience

Simplicity Games, Programista Unity3D, November 2017 – February 2018

- **Ski Jump Challange** (Android, iOS)
 - o Created the user interface based on the designer's guidelines
 - Collaborated with teams of developers, artists, and designers

Primebit Games S.A., Senior Unity Developer, February 2019 – Present

- Clash II (PC)
 - Led the development team
 - Created the entire game architecture
 - Created a map editor for the design team
 - o Optimized memory usage using Profiler and Memory Profiler, implemented resource loading with Addressables
 - Developed a unit management system
 - Developed a unit skill system
 - Developed a unit equipment system

 Developed a UI window management system and animations using the DOTween library

• **Inside Grass** (Android, iOS)

Fixed existing bugs

• **8 Minute Empire** (Nintendo Switch)

 Ported a mobile game to the Nintendo Switch platform, including adding gamepad support, adjusting controls, and user interface

• Caveman Chuck (Nintendo Switch)

- Ported a mobile game to the Nintendo Switch platform, including adding gamepad support, adjusting controls, UI, and save system
- Supervised the certification process

• **Dark Tower** (Nintendo Switch)

- Ported a mobile game to the Nintendo Switch platform, including adding gamepad support, adjusting controls, UI, and save system
- Supervised the certification process

• **VRFitness** (Samsung Gear VR)

- Developed two games for Samsung Gear VR headsets in collaboration with stationary bicycles and for an external client
- o Created a multiplayer module offering races with other players on a local Wi-Fi network
- Optimized performance to ensure smooth gameplay

Education

Computer Science, Master's Degree, Rzeszów University of Technology, February 2018 – July 2019

 Master's thesis: "Artificial Intelligence Algorithms Solving the Shortest Path Problem," grade: 5

Computer Science, Bachelor's Degree, Rzeszów University of Technology, October 2014 – February 2018

- Overall GPA: 4.6
- Bachelor's thesis: "Application of Artificial Intelligence Algorithms in Computer Games," grade: 5